[
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Hello in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Hola",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Adiós",
      "Gracias",
      "Por favor"
    ],
    "explanation": "Hola means Hello.",
    "keywords": [
      "greetings"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Good morning in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Buenos días",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Buenas noches",
      "Buenas tardes",
      "Buenas mañanas"
    ],
    "explanation": "Buenos días means Good morning.",
    "keywords": [
      "greetings"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Good night in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Buenas noches",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Buenas tardes",
      "Adiós",
      "Hasta mañana"
    ],
    "explanation": "Buenas noches means Good night.",
    "keywords": [
      "greetings"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Good afternoon in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Buenas tardes",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Buenas noches",
      "Buenos días",
      "Adiós"
    ],
    "explanation": "Buenas tardes means Good afternoon.",
    "keywords": [
      "greetings"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Goodbye in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Adiós",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hola",
      "Gracias",
      "De nada"
    ],
    "explanation": "Adiós means Goodbye.",
    "keywords": [
      "greetings"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say See you later in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Hasta luego",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hasta pronto",
      "Hasta mañana",
      "Adiós"
    ],
    "explanation": "Hasta luego means See you later.",
    "keywords": [
      "greetings"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say See you tomorrow in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Hasta mañana",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hasta luego",
      "Buenas noches",
      "Nos vemos"
    ],
    "explanation": "Hasta mañana means See you tomorrow.",
    "keywords": [
      "greetings"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Please in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Por favor",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gracias",
      "Perdón",
      "Hola"
    ],
    "explanation": "Por favor means Please.",
    "keywords": [
      "greetings"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Thank you in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Gracias",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "De nada",
      "Hola",
      "Por favor"
    ],
    "explanation": "Gracias means Thank you.",
    "keywords": [
      "greetings"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say You're welcome in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "De nada",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gracias",
      "Por favor",
      "Adiós"
    ],
    "explanation": "De nada means You're welcome.",
    "keywords": [
      "greetings"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Excuse me in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Perdón",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gracias",
      "Hola",
      "Adiós"
    ],
    "explanation": "Perdón means Excuse me.",
    "keywords": [
      "greetings"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say How are you? in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "¿Cómo estás?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "¿Dónde estás?",
      "¿Qué hora es?",
      "¿Quién eres?"
    ],
    "explanation": "¿Cómo estás? means How are you?",
    "keywords": [
      "greetings"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say What’s your name? in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "¿Cómo te llamas?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "¿Cómo estás?",
      "¿Dónde vives?",
      "¿Quién eres?"
    ],
    "explanation": "¿Cómo te llamas? means What’s your name?",
    "keywords": [
      "greetings"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Nice to meet you in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Mucho gusto",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "De nada",
      "Por favor",
      "Hola"
    ],
    "explanation": "Mucho gusto means Nice to meet you.",
    "keywords": [
      "greetings"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Welcome in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Bienvenido",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hola",
      "Gracias",
      "Adiós"
    ],
    "explanation": "Bienvenido means Welcome.",
    "keywords": [
      "greetings"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Long time no see in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Cuánto tiempo",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hasta luego",
      "Hasta mañana",
      "Adiós"
    ],
    "explanation": "Cuánto tiempo is used like Long time no see.",
    "keywords": [
      "greetings"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Take care in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Cuídate",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hola",
      "Adiós",
      "Mucho gusto"
    ],
    "explanation": "Cuídate means Take care.",
    "keywords": [
      "greetings"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Airport in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Aeropuerto",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Calle",
      "Estación",
      "Avión"
    ],
    "explanation": "Aeropuerto means Airport.",
    "keywords": [
      "travel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Train in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Tren",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Metro",
      "Taxi",
      "Avión"
    ],
    "explanation": "Tren means Train.",
    "keywords": [
      "travel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Bus in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Autobús",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Carro",
      "Taxi",
      "Bicicleta"
    ],
    "explanation": "Autobús means Bus.",
    "keywords": [
      "travel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Ticket in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Boleto",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Viaje",
      "Pase",
      "Ruta"
    ],
    "explanation": "Boleto means Ticket.",
    "keywords": [
      "travel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Luggage in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Equipaje",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Bolsa",
      "Ropa",
      "Regalo"
    ],
    "explanation": "Equipaje means Luggage.",
    "keywords": [
      "travel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Hotel in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Hotel",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Casa",
      "Apartamento",
      "Hostal"
    ],
    "explanation": "Hotel means Hotel.",
    "keywords": [
      "travel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Beach in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Playa",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Río",
      "Montaña",
      "Bosque"
    ],
    "explanation": "Playa means Beach.",
    "keywords": [
      "travel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Map in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Mapa",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Camino",
      "Guía",
      "Lugar"
    ],
    "explanation": "Mapa means Map.",
    "keywords": [
      "travel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Passport in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Pasaporte",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Documento",
      "Visa",
      "Identificación"
    ],
    "explanation": "Pasaporte means Passport.",
    "keywords": [
      "travel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Taxi in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Taxi",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tren",
      "Autobús",
      "Coche"
    ],
    "explanation": "Taxi means Taxi.",
    "keywords": [
      "travel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Left in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Izquierda",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Derecha",
      "Arriba",
      "Abajo"
    ],
    "explanation": "Izquierda means Left.",
    "keywords": [
      "travel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Right in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Derecha",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Izquierda",
      "Adentro",
      "Afuera"
    ],
    "explanation": "Derecha means Right.",
    "keywords": [
      "travel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Street in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Calle",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Puente",
      "Pueblo",
      "Carretera"
    ],
    "explanation": "Calle means Street.",
    "keywords": [
      "travel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say City in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Ciudad",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "País",
      "Barrio",
      "Pueblo"
    ],
    "explanation": "Ciudad means City.",
    "keywords": [
      "travel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Where is the bathroom? in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "¿Dónde está el baño?",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "¿Dónde está la playa?",
      "¿Dónde está la calle?",
      "¿Dónde está mi hotel?"
    ],
    "explanation": "¿Dónde está el baño? means Where is the bathroom?",
    "keywords": [
      "travel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say I need help in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Necesito ayuda",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Necesito comida",
      "Necesito hotel",
      "Necesito taxi"
    ],
    "explanation": "Necesito ayuda means I need help.",
    "keywords": [
      "travel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say I'm lost in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Estoy perdido",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Estoy cansado",
      "Estoy aquí",
      "Estoy listo"
    ],
    "explanation": "Estoy perdido means I'm lost.",
    "keywords": [
      "travel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Bread in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Pan",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Agua",
      "Sal",
      "Leche"
    ],
    "explanation": "Pan means Bread.",
    "keywords": [
      "food"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Water in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Agua",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pan",
      "Jugo",
      "Vino"
    ],
    "explanation": "Agua means Water.",
    "keywords": [
      "food"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Milk in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Leche",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Agua",
      "Pan",
      "Carne"
    ],
    "explanation": "Leche means Milk.",
    "keywords": [
      "food"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Chicken in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Pollo",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Carne",
      "Pavo",
      "Pescado"
    ],
    "explanation": "Pollo means Chicken.",
    "keywords": [
      "food"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Fish in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Pescado",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pollo",
      "Carne",
      "Pan"
    ],
    "explanation": "Pescado means Fish.",
    "keywords": [
      "food"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Meat in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Carne",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pan",
      "Pescado",
      "Pollo"
    ],
    "explanation": "Carne means Meat.",
    "keywords": [
      "food"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Rice in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Arroz",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pan",
      "Pasta",
      "Queso"
    ],
    "explanation": "Arroz means Rice.",
    "keywords": [
      "food"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Cheese in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Queso",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pasta",
      "Carne",
      "Huevo"
    ],
    "explanation": "Queso means Cheese.",
    "keywords": [
      "food"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Egg in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Huevo",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Queso",
      "Pan",
      "Agua"
    ],
    "explanation": "Huevo means Egg.",
    "keywords": [
      "food"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Fruit in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Fruta",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Verdura",
      "Carne",
      "Pan"
    ],
    "explanation": "Fruta means Fruit.",
    "keywords": [
      "food"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Apple in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Manzana",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Naranja",
      "Uva",
      "Pera"
    ],
    "explanation": "Manzana means Apple.",
    "keywords": [
      "food"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Orange in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Naranja",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Manzana",
      "Limón",
      "Pera"
    ],
    "explanation": "Naranja means Orange.",
    "keywords": [
      "food"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Ice cream in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Helado",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Frío",
      "Nieve",
      "Dulce"
    ],
    "explanation": "Helado means Ice cream.",
    "keywords": [
      "food"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Sugar in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Azúcar",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Sal",
      "Miel",
      "Leche"
    ],
    "explanation": "Azúcar means Sugar.",
    "keywords": [
      "food"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Salt in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Sal",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Azúcar",
      "Agua",
      "Leche"
    ],
    "explanation": "Sal means Salt.",
    "keywords": [
      "food"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Breakfast in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Desayuno",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Almuerzo",
      "Cena",
      "Comida"
    ],
    "explanation": "Desayuno means Breakfast.",
    "keywords": [
      "food"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Lunch in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Almuerzo",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Desayuno",
      "Cena",
      "Comida"
    ],
    "explanation": "Almuerzo means Lunch.",
    "keywords": [
      "food"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say To eat in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Comer",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Beber",
      "Dormir",
      "Hablar"
    ],
    "explanation": "Comer means To eat.",
    "keywords": [
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say To drink in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Beber",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Comer",
      "Caminar",
      "Leer"
    ],
    "explanation": "Beber means To drink.",
    "keywords": [
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say To go in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Ir",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Venir",
      "Tener",
      "Ser"
    ],
    "explanation": "Ir means To go.",
    "keywords": [
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say To be (permanent) in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Ser",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Estar",
      "Ir",
      "Hacer"
    ],
    "explanation": "Ser is the permanent form of To be.",
    "keywords": [
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say To be (temporary) in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Estar",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ser",
      "Ir",
      "Venir"
    ],
    "explanation": "Estar is the temporary form of To be.",
    "keywords": [
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say To have in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Tener",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hacer",
      "Ir",
      "Ser"
    ],
    "explanation": "Tener means To have.",
    "keywords": [
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say To do / To make in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Hacer",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Decir",
      "Tener",
      "Ser"
    ],
    "explanation": "Hacer means To do or To make.",
    "keywords": [
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say To speak in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Hablar",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Leer",
      "Escribir",
      "Comer"
    ],
    "explanation": "Hablar means To speak.",
    "keywords": [
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say To read in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Leer",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Escribir",
      "Correr",
      "Ir"
    ],
    "explanation": "Leer means To read.",
    "keywords": [
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say To write in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Escribir",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Leer",
      "Hablar",
      "Dormir"
    ],
    "explanation": "Escribir means To write.",
    "keywords": [
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say To sleep in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Dormir",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Correr",
      "Jugar",
      "Leer"
    ],
    "explanation": "Dormir means To sleep.",
    "keywords": [
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say To run in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Correr",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Caminar",
      "Saltar",
      "Leer"
    ],
    "explanation": "Correr means To run.",
    "keywords": [
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say To walk in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Caminar",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Correr",
      "Beber",
      "Comer"
    ],
    "explanation": "Caminar means To walk.",
    "keywords": [
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say To understand in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Entender",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Aprender",
      "Comer",
      "Correr"
    ],
    "explanation": "Entender means To understand.",
    "keywords": [
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say To learn in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Aprender",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Entender",
      "Correr",
      "Dormir"
    ],
    "explanation": "Aprender means To learn.",
    "keywords": [
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say To want in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Querer",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Tener",
      "Ser",
      "Ir"
    ],
    "explanation": "Querer means To want.",
    "keywords": [
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say To live in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Vivir",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ser",
      "Tener",
      "Ir"
    ],
    "explanation": "Vivir means To live.",
    "keywords": [
      "verbs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say House in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Casa",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Carro",
      "Calle",
      "Ciudad"
    ],
    "explanation": "Casa means House.",
    "keywords": [
      "basic vocabulary"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Car in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Coche",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Casa",
      "Puerta",
      "Mesa"
    ],
    "explanation": "Coche means Car.",
    "keywords": [
      "basic vocabulary"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Door in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Puerta",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mesa",
      "Silla",
      "Ventana"
    ],
    "explanation": "Puerta means Door.",
    "keywords": [
      "basic vocabulary"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Window in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Ventana",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Puerta",
      "Mesa",
      "Cama"
    ],
    "explanation": "Ventana means Window.",
    "keywords": [
      "basic vocabulary"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Table in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Mesa",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Silla",
      "Puerta",
      "Ventana"
    ],
    "explanation": "Mesa means Table.",
    "keywords": [
      "basic vocabulary"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Chair in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Silla",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mesa",
      "Cama",
      "Puerta"
    ],
    "explanation": "Silla means Chair.",
    "keywords": [
      "basic vocabulary"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Bed in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Cama",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mesa",
      "Silla",
      "Puerta"
    ],
    "explanation": "Cama means Bed.",
    "keywords": [
      "basic vocabulary"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Book in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Libro",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Mesa",
      "Silla",
      "Casa"
    ],
    "explanation": "Libro means Book.",
    "keywords": [
      "basic vocabulary"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Pen in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Pluma",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Lápiz",
      "Bolsa",
      "Casa"
    ],
    "explanation": "Pluma means Pen.",
    "keywords": [
      "basic vocabulary"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Pencil in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Lápiz",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pluma",
      "Libro",
      "Casa"
    ],
    "explanation": "Lápiz means Pencil.",
    "keywords": [
      "basic vocabulary"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Phone in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Teléfono",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cámara",
      "Mesa",
      "Puerta"
    ],
    "explanation": "Teléfono means Phone.",
    "keywords": [
      "basic vocabulary"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Friend in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Amigo",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hermano",
      "Padre",
      "Madre"
    ],
    "explanation": "Amigo means Friend.",
    "keywords": [
      "basic vocabulary"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Family in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Familia",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Hogar",
      "Amigos",
      "Padres"
    ],
    "explanation": "Familia means Family.",
    "keywords": [
      "basic vocabulary"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say School in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Escuela",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Libro",
      "Mesa",
      "Clase"
    ],
    "explanation": "Escuela means School.",
    "keywords": [
      "basic vocabulary"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Teacher in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Maestro",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Estudiante",
      "Amigo",
      "Jefe"
    ],
    "explanation": "Maestro means Teacher.",
    "keywords": [
      "basic vocabulary"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Student in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Estudiante",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Maestro",
      "Amigo",
      "Hermano"
    ],
    "explanation": "Estudiante means Student.",
    "keywords": [
      "basic vocabulary"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say One in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Uno",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Dos",
      "Tres",
      "Cuatro"
    ],
    "explanation": "Uno means One.",
    "keywords": [
      "numbers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Two in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Dos",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Uno",
      "Tres",
      "Cinco"
    ],
    "explanation": "Dos means Two.",
    "keywords": [
      "numbers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Three in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Tres",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Uno",
      "Dos",
      "Cuatro"
    ],
    "explanation": "Tres means Three.",
    "keywords": [
      "numbers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Four in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Cuatro",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cinco",
      "Tres",
      "Dos"
    ],
    "explanation": "Cuatro means Four.",
    "keywords": [
      "numbers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Five in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Cinco",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cuatro",
      "Seis",
      "Dos"
    ],
    "explanation": "Cinco means Five.",
    "keywords": [
      "numbers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Six in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Seis",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Siete",
      "Cinco",
      "Cuatro"
    ],
    "explanation": "Seis means Six.",
    "keywords": [
      "numbers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Seven in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Siete",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ocho",
      "Seis",
      "Cinco"
    ],
    "explanation": "Siete means Seven.",
    "keywords": [
      "numbers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Eight in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Ocho",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Siete",
      "Nueve",
      "Diez"
    ],
    "explanation": "Ocho means Eight.",
    "keywords": [
      "numbers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Nine in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Nueve",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ocho",
      "Diez",
      "Once"
    ],
    "explanation": "Nueve means Nine.",
    "keywords": [
      "numbers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Ten in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Diez",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Ocho",
      "Nueve",
      "Once"
    ],
    "explanation": "Diez means Ten.",
    "keywords": [
      "numbers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Twenty in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Veinte",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Treinta",
      "Doce",
      "Ciento"
    ],
    "explanation": "Veinte means Twenty.",
    "keywords": [
      "numbers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Thirty in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Treinta",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cuarenta",
      "Veinte",
      "Cincuenta"
    ],
    "explanation": "Treinta means Thirty.",
    "keywords": [
      "numbers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Forty in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Cuarenta",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Treinta",
      "Veinte",
      "Cincuenta"
    ],
    "explanation": "Cuarenta means Forty.",
    "keywords": [
      "numbers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say Fifty in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Cincuenta",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cuarenta",
      "Setenta",
      "Treinta"
    ],
    "explanation": "Cincuenta means Fifty.",
    "keywords": [
      "numbers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say One hundred in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Cien",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cincuenta",
      "Ciento uno",
      "Mil"
    ],
    "explanation": "Cien means One hundred.",
    "keywords": [
      "numbers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Spanish",
    "question": "How do you say One thousand in Spanish?",
    "correctAnswer": "Mil",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cien",
      "Ciento",
      "Millón"
    ],
    "explanation": "Mil means One thousand.",
    "keywords": [
      "numbers"
    ]
  }
]